// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q030: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Product brochures and samples will be ------ to visitors at the upcoming new product presentation.',
      choices: ['imported', 'received', 'obtained', 'distributed'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['distributed'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'At least three years of ------ experience is required to apply for the welder position listed on the job posting site.',
      choices: ['professional', 'profession', 'professionalism', 'professionally'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['professional'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'After a thorough review, ------ minor changes were made to the building purchase agreement.',
      choices: ['every', 'much', 'a few', 'each'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['a few'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Last year the Hudson Art Museum ------ a quarterly newsletter to its members.',
      choices: ['published', 'corresponded', 'resided', 'intended'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['published'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ the renovation of the second floor has been completed, the Human Resources Department can return to its original workplace.',
      choices: ['Now that', 'Consequently', 'Due to', 'Regarding'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Now that'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'New employees in the Quality Control Department will be given their ------ by their immediate supervisors next Monday.',
      choices: ['assigned', 'assign', 'assignment', 'assigns'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['assignment'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The deadline for submitting proposals for new construction in the Stanley district has been ------ by one week.',
      choices: ['expanded', 'published', 'relocated', 'extended'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['extended'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ those who pass the first round of selection will receive an email with instructions for the second round.',
      choices: ['If', 'Only', 'Upon', 'Before'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Only'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If you do not renew your fitness center membership, it will ------ on June 30.',
      choices: ['extend', 'pursue', 'undergo', 'expire'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['expire'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Only auto parts that have passed ------ tests will be shipped from this factory.',
      choices: ['spacious', 'rigorous', 'acclaimed', 'cautious'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['rigorous'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}